<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Damn Vulnerable Mobile ICC</string>

    <string name="welcome_msg">Welcome to DVM-ICC!</string>
    <string name="introductionHeading">Introduction</string>
    <string name="introduction">
        Damn Vulnerable Mobile -  Inter Component Communication is an intentionally insecure
        Android image, created to be an educational tool to teach people about cyberattacks and
        vulnerabilities related to Inter Component Communication (ICC) in Android.

        \n\nThis educational tool is aimed at penetration testers, app developers and tech savvy
        people alike. It has four different operation modes that can be used to complete
        challenges, tailored to users with more or less experience.

        \n\nIndividual vulnerabilities are explored through challenges. Each challenge
        consists of an authentic scenario of a malware attacking a vulnerable application. You
        have to identify the malware and vulnerable apps, then start the apps and use the malware
        to perform an attack and observe its effects.

        \n\nDepending on the user mode, you will benefit from an explanation of the vulnerability,
        how to identify it and of various ways to fix it. You are able to see the attack happen
        and you have to answer various questions to complete the challenge.
    </string>
    <string name="whyICCHeading">Importance of ICC</string>
    <string name="whyICC">
        We chose to explore Inter Component Communication vulnerabilities on Android in this project
        due to the current state of mobile application security.

        \n\nFirstly, insecure inter-component communication is a high-risk vulnerability, and it is
        more dangerous than insecure storage, insecure transmission of data, inadequate brute force
        protection or other common vulnerabilities, according to this
        <a href="https://www.ptsecurity.com/upload/corporate/ww-en/analytics/Mobile-Application-Vulnerabilities-and-Threats-2019-eng.pdf">2019 report</a>.

        \n\nSecondly, this type of vulnerability is relatively common. It can be found in 29
        percent of mobile apps according, and the average Android application has 1.1 ICC
        vulnerabilities. according the report linked above.

        \n\nThirdly, while the overwhelming majority of vulnerabilities of other types are
        introduced in apps through the use of third-party libraries and rarely through developer
        code, ICC vulnerabilities differ. According to <a href ="https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/abstract/document/8936901">this paper</a>
        , between a third and a half of ICC vulnerabilities come from developer code. Therefore,
        education about ICC vulnerabilities addressed to developers would lead to less
        vulnerabilities of this type.

        \n\nFourthly, ICC vulnerabilities are not showcased in detail in real word projects
        similar to ours. Damn Vulnerable Web Application does not cover any Inter Process
        vulnerabilities and TryHackMe.com has no dedicated activities on this topic. Damn Insecure
        and Vulnerable App has 2 activities that exploit badly implemented communication
        between components. However, they do not show in detail all the possible ICC vulnerabilities
        and threats.
    </string>
</resources>